Register of the Polish Subject Collection, 1918-2014
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials
  - "Druga Emigracja Stanislawa Mikolajczyka" "Poznanczycy. Wspomnienia o Powstaniu Wielkopolskim", 1996 (Box-folder 65: 7)
  - "Z Chlopa Prezes Witold Hatka", 1996 (Box-folder 65: 8)
  - John Paul II - trip to Cuba, 1998 (Box-folder 65: 9)
  - John Paul II - trip to Cuba, 1998 (Box-folder 65: 10)
  - John Paul II, Undated (Box-folder 65: 11)
  - Dziennik - John Paul II, Undated (Box-folder 65: 12)
  - John Paul II - trip to Cuba, 1998 (Box-folder 65: 13)
  - John Paul II - trip to Cuba, 1998 (Box-folder 65: 14)
    Havana Mass - "A lighy for the nations" documentary
  - Powodz w Polsce - Apel do Serc, 1997 (Box-folder 65: 15)
  - Polish-German Relations, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Communist Party Political Line, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 66: 2)
  - Communist Party Political Line, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 66: 3)
  - Communist Party Political Line, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 66: 4)
  - Solidarity Message, 1981 (Box-folder 66: 5)
    Message of the Solidarity Convention of the Workers of Eastern Europe in Gdansk
  - Coalition Parties - Documents, 1981 (Box-folder 66: 6)
  - Scouts Movement, 1981 (Box-folder 66: 7)
    Statut Zwiazku Harcerskiego
  - Reform of Government Administration, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 66: 8)
  - "Aktualnosci" Communist Party Warsaw Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 66: 9)
    Komitet Warszawski PZPR
  - Daily Reports of the Warsaw Party Information Center, 1982 (Box-folder 66: 10)
  - Counterrevolution in Hungary and Poland, 1982 (Box-folder 66: 11)
  - Bulletin of the Communist Party Warsaw Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 66: 12)
  - Church Doctrine, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 66: 13)
  - Labor Unions, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 66: 14)
  - Ticket Prices, 1984 (Box-folder 66: 15)
    PKP I PKS nowe ceny biletow
  - Health Care, 1985 (Box-folder 66: 16)
  - Non-Proletarian Protest Movements in Capitalist Countries, 1985 (Box-folder 66: 17)
  - Culture, 1985 (Box-folder 66: 18)
  - Revolution in Ethiopia, 1985 (Box-folder 66: 19)
  - Bulletin of the Communist Party Szczecin Committee, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 66: 20)
  - Polish Army, 1986 (Box-folder 66: 21)
  - Polish-Soviet Trade, 1986 (Box-folder 66: 22)
  - Trybuna Ludu, 1987 (Box-folder 66: 23)
  - Elections, 1989 (Box-folder 66: 24)
  - Wroclas Breslau, Undated (Box-folder 66: 25)
  - Marian Gliwa - Polish notebook, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 67: 1)
    School notebook for the Polish language
  - Marian Gliwa - Polish notebooks, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 67: 2)
  - Marian Gliwa - notebooks, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 67: 3)
    English composition and Polish essays
  - Marian Gliwa - notebook, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 67: 4)
    Zeszyt ksiazek przeczytanych
  - Economic Reform, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 67: 5)
  - Economic Reform, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 67: 6)
  - Sikorski's Funeral, 1993 (Box-folder 67: 7)
    Press publications on the funeral of General Wladyslaw Sikorski - Dziennik Polski, Czas Krakowski, Echo Krakowa
  - Szymborska - Nobel, 1996 (Box-folder 67: 8)
    Press publications on Wislawa Szymborska winning the Nobel Prize
  - Polish Army, 1997 (Box-folder 67: 9)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Gazeta Wyborcza, 1997 (Box-folder 68: 1--4)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Slowo Polskie, 1997 (Box-folder 68: 5--6)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Wieczor Wroclawia, 1997 (Box-folder 68: 7)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Gazeta Wroclawska, 1997 (Box-folder 68: 8)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Other Newspapers, 1997 (Box-folder 68: 9)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Catholic Newspapers, 1997 (Box-folder 69: 1--2)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Catholic Periodicals, 1997 (Box-folder 69: 3--4)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Other Press Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 69: 5--6)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Promotional Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 69: 8)
  - John Paul II in Poland - Foreign Press, 1997 (Box-folder 69: 9)
    Press Materials, Promotional Materials, Flyers
  - 46th Eucharistic Congress - Publications, 1997 (Box-folder 70: 1--6)
  - 46th Eucharistic Congress - Promotional Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 70: 7--8)
  - Election Materials, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 71: 1--4)
  - Periodicals - Ziemia Klodzka, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Foreign Newspapers, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Newspapers - Gazeta Wroclawska, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - Newspapers - Other, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - Newspapers - Press Review, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 9)
  - Newspapers - Slowo Polskie, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 10)
  - Newspapers - Wieczor Wroclawski, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 11)
  - Newspapers - Wieczor Wroclawski, 1997 (Box-folder 71: 12)
  - Topography - Map - Geologiczna Karta Polsko-Szlazkiego Zaglebia Weglowego, 1893 (Box-folder 72: 1)
  - Topography - Map of Gory Swietokrzyskie, 1919 (Box-folder 72: 2)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1919-1937 (Box-folder 72: 3)
    Kupony na Chleb, "Wybuch Pokoju", "This Was Warsaw"
  - Pamphlets - Upper Silesia Plebiscite, 1921 (Box-folder 72: 4)
  - Polish Constitution - French, 1921 (Box-folder 72: 5)
  - Topography - Map of Bitkow Oil Region, 1923 (Box-folder 72: 6)
  - Topography - Russian Report in Polish, 1928 (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - Nationalization - Documents, 1930-1949 (Box-folder 72: 8)
    Akta Glownej Komisji do Spraw Upanstwowienia Przedsiebiorstw - Spolka Akcyjna do Eksploatacji Panstwowego Monopolu Zapalczanego
  - Nationalization - Documents, 1930-1949 (Box-folder 72: 9)
  - Ministerstwo Spraw Wojskowych - Regulations, 1931 (Box-folder 72: 10)
  - Press Materials - Armia Krajowa, 1944 (Box-folder 72: 11)
    Photocopies
  - Polish Constitution - Addresses in House of Representatives, 1945 (Box-folder 72: 12)
    79th Congress - Polish Constitution Day - One hundred fifty-fourth anniversary of the independence of Poland
  - Nationalization - Documents, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 72: 13)
    Protokol Zdawczo-Odbiorczy - Centralny Zarzad Przemyslu Drzewnego - Piskie Zaklady Przemyslu Drzewnego
  - Nationalization - Fabryka "Alva", 1950-1962 (Box-folder 72: 14)
    Fabryka "Alva" w Brodach Malych
  - Jungdeutsche Partei fur Polen - Documents, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 73: 1)
  - Sikorski Institute, 1945 (Box-folder 73: 2)
    Instytut Historyczny im. Generala Sikorskiego - Umowa, protokol
  - Trybuna Dolnoslaska, 1948 (Box-folder 73: 3)
  - Trybuna Dolnoslaska, 1948 (Box-folder 73: 4)
  - Trybuna Dolnoslaska, 1948 (Box-folder 73: 5)
  - Trybuna Wolnosci - Dodatek, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 73: 6)
    "Na czym polega istota odchylenia prawicowego I nacjonalistycznego w naszej partii"
  - Boleslaw Bierut, 1952 (Box-folder 73: 7)
  - Boleslaw Bierut, 1953 (Box-folder 73: 8)
  - Trybuna Ludu, 1955 (Box-folder 73: 9)
  - Catechisms and Notebook, 1957-1992 (Box-folder 73: 10)
  - Warszawki Zwiazek Literatow Polskich, 1968 (Box-folder 73: 11)
    Stenogram z nadzwyczajnego walnego zebrania oddzialu warszawskiego zwiazku literatow polskich
  - Polish United Workers' Party Policy Outline, 1974 (Box-folder 73: 12)
    Polish United Workers Party Central Committee; 30 Anniversary of Polish People's Republic, Outline of the party's policies
  - Spolem we Wroclawiu, 1980 (Box-folder 73: 13)
    Kompleksowy system sterowania jakoscia pracy
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 73: 14)
  - Postcards, 1992 (Box-folder 73: 15)
  - Konkordat Polska - Stolica Apostolska, 1998 (Box-folder 73: 16)
  - Biala Ksiega, 1981 (Box-folder 74: 1)
    Fakty, Informacje, Wypowiedzi, Cytaty dotyczace dzialanosci NSZZ "Solidarnosc"
  - Biala Ksiega, 1981 (Box-folder 74: 2)
  - Biezaca Informacja Polityczna, 1981 (Box-folder 74: 3)
    Wydzial Pracy Ideowo-Wychowawczej KC PZPR
  - List of detainees, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 74: 4)
    Letter to Committee in Support of Solidarity
  - List of detainees, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 74: 5)
  - Spoleczne przeglady warunkow pracy, 1988 (Box-folder 74: 6)
    Teczka Aktowa
  - Spoleczne przeglady warunkow pracy, 1988 (Box-folder 74: 7)
  - Periodicals - Edukacja, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 74: 8)
    Solidarity Teachers Union; Wroclaw Regional newspaper from the transition period
  - Periodicals - Glos Uniwesytetu, 1990 (Box-folder 74: 9)
    Wroclaw University student publication
  - Monitor Polski, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 10)
  - Polish emblem, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 11)
    Found in the building of the Ministry of Defence
  - Constitution of Poland, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 12)
  - Constitution of Poland, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 13)
  - Constitution of Poland - Bulletin, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 14)
  - Constitution of Poland - Referendum Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 15)
  - Elections - Jaworzno, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 1)
  - Elections - Katowice, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 2)
  - Election Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 3)
  - Election Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 4)
  - Election Materials - Online, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 5)
  - Election Materials - Online, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 6)
  - Election Materials - Sejm, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 7)
  - Election Materials - Sejm, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 8)
  - Elections - Krakow, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 9)
  - Elections - Krakow, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Elections - Warsaw, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 11)
  - Elections - Lublin, 1997 (Box-folder 75: 12)
  - Publications - Biala Ksiega, 1980-81 (Box-folder 76: 1)
    Book for professional use by the Warsaw military containing information about the development of Solidarity as a political movement
  - Publications - Informacja, 1981 (Box-folder 76: 2)
    Report on a Solidarity document (Kierunki dzialania Zwiazku w obecnej sytuacji kraju), pre-report and report form the department of propaganda of the Polish military on the I Convention of Delegates of Solidarity
  - Newspapers - Express Wieczorny, 1981 (Box-folder 76: 3)
  - Publications - Przeciwko Narodowi, 1982 (Box-folder 76: 4)
    Selection of articles about the activity of antisocialist forces in Poland part 2, volume 2
  - Newspapers - Kongres Intelektualistow, 1983 (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - Publications - Przeglad dzialanosci kosciola, 1988 (Box-folder 76: 6)
    Report on the activities of the Roman Catholic Church in Poland - for the ideological department of the PZPR
  - Newspapers - Express Wieczorny, 1989 (Box-folder 76: 7)
  - Newspapers - Express Wieczorny, 1989 (Box-folder 76: 8)
  - Newspapers - Gazeta Wyborcza, 1989 (Box-folder 76: 9)
  - Newspapers - Gazeta Wyborcza, 1989 (Box-folder 76: 10)
  - Newspapers - Konfrontacje, 1989 (Box-folder 77: 1)
  - Newspapers - Perspektywy, 1989 (Box-folder 77: 2)
  - Newspapers - Trybuna Ludu, 1989 (Box-folder 77: 3)
  - Newspapers - Zmiany, 1989 (Box-folder 77: 4)
  - Newspapers - Others, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 77: 5)
    Czas!, Czas Krakowski, Gazeta Gdanska, Gazeta Krakowska, Gazeta Samordzadowa, Inaczej, Kurier Polski, Nowo-Stara Gazeta (przed) Wyborcza, Satyrykon
  - Newspapers - Reporter, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 77: 6)
  - Newspapers - Zycie Warszawy, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 78: 1)
  - Newspapers - Gazeta International, 1990 (Box-folder 78: 2)
  - Newspapers - Konfrontacje, 1990 (Box-folder 78: 3)
  - Newspapers - Po Prostu, 1990 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Election Materials - General Materials, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 5)
    Local elections in Poland - wybory samorzadowe
  - Local Elections - Akcja Wyborcza Solidarnosc (AWS), 1998 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Local Elections - Akcja Wyborcza Solidarnosc (AWS), 1998 (Box-folder 78: 7)
  - Local Elections - Other Parties, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 8)
    Independent candidates, MRS, others
  - Local Elections - Przymierze Spoleczne, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 9)
  - Local Elections - Rodzina Polska, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 10)
  - Local Elections - Ruch Patriotyczny Ojczyzna, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 11)
  - Local Elections - Sojusz Lewicy Demokratycznej (SLD), 1998 (Box-folder 78: 12)
  - Local Elections - Unia Wolnosci, 1998 (Box-folder 78: 13)
  - NATO - Publications, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 01-02.1997 (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 3.1997 (Box-folder 79: 3)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 3.1997 (Box-folder 79: 4)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 4.1997 (Box-folder 79: 5)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 4.1997 (Box-folder 79: 6)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 5.1997 (Box-folder 79: 7)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 6.1997 (Box-folder 79: 8)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 6.1996 (Box-folder 79: 9)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 7.1997 (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 7.1997 (Box-folder 80: 2)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 8.1997 (Box-folder 80: 3)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 9.1997 (Box-folder 80: 4)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 9.1997 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 10.1997 (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 11.1997 (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 12.1997 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - NATO - Official Publications, 1997 (Box-folder 80: 9)
  - NATO - Polish American Congress, 1997 (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 1.1998 (Box-folder 80: 11)
  - NATO - Publications, 01-02.1998 (Box-folder 80: 12)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 2.1998 (Box-folder 80: 13)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 3.1998 (Box-folder 80: 14)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 3.1998 (Box-folder 80: 15)
  - NATO - Publications, 03-04.1998 (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 4.1998 (Box-folder 81: 2)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 5.1998 (Box-folder 81: 3)
  - NATO - Publications, 05-08.1998 (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 6.1998 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 7.1998 (Box-folder 81: 6)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 8.1998 (Box-folder 81: 7)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 09-10.1998 (Box-folder 81: 8)
  - NATO - Publications, 09-12.1998 (Box-folder 81: 9)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 11-12.1998 (Box-folder 81: 10)
  - NATO - Protocols, 1998 (Box-folder 81: 11)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 01-02.1999 (Box-folder 81: 12)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 3.1999 (Box-folder 81: 13)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 4.1999 (Box-folder 81: 14)
  - NATO - E-mails with publications, 05-12.1999 (Box-folder 81: 15)
  - IX Nadzwyczajny Zjazd PZPR - Book, 1981 (Box-folder 82: 1)
    Nowe Drogi
  - Economic Reform - Narodowy Plan Spoleczno-Gospodarczy, 1983 (Box-folder 82: 2)
    National Socio-Economic Plan 1983-1985
  - Economic Reform - Report, 1987 (Box-folder 82: 3)
    Kadra Kierownicza Przedsiebiorstw Wobec Reformy
  - W Marszu do Niepodleglosci - Lyrics, 1995 (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - NATO - Publications, 1999 (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - Presidential Elections - Kalinowski, Jaroslaw, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 6)
  - Presidential Elections - Kwasniewski, Aleksander, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 7)
  - Presidential Elections - Olechowski, Andrzej, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - Presidential Elections - Other Candidates, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 9)
  - Presidential Elections - Walesa, Lech, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 10)
  - Katyn - Memoirs, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 11)
    Janina Szestakowska
  - Polish-German Relations - Application, 2000 (Box-folder 82: 12)
    Fundacja "Polsko-Niemieckie Pojednanie"
  - NATO - Publications, Undated (Box-folder 82: 13)
  - NATO - Publications, Undated (Box-folder 82: 14)
  - Diplomacy - Book, 1929 (Box-folder 83: 1)
    "Dyplomacja Dawnej Polski" - ilustracja archiwalna w dziale MSZ na Powszechnej Wystawie Krajowej
  - Diplomacy - Book, 1932 (Box-folder 83: 2)
    "Deutschland, Polen und der 'Korridor'"
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1932 (Box-folder 83: 3)
    "Le Travail Des Eclaireuses Polonaises"
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1935 (Box-folder 83: 4)
    "Antek Cwaniak Ksiazka o Zuchach" Aleksander Kaminski
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1938 (Box-folder 83: 5)
    "Skauting dla chlopcow" Lord Baden-Powell of Gilwell
  - Diplomacy - Wiadomosci Sportowe, 1939 (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1947 (Box-folder 83: 7)
    "Ksiega Harcow" Tom 11
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1961 (Box-folder 83: 8)
    "Ognie I ogniska: Drogi I przemiany harcerstwa polskiego" Kazimierz Kozniewski
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1966 (Box-folder 83: 9)
    "Gawedy z Druzynowym" Henryk Glass
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1972 (Box-folder 83: 10)
    "Harcerka w Mundurze" Irma Paluchowa
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1972 (Box-folder 83: 11)
    "Organizacja Harcerek"
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1973 (Box-folder 83: 12)
    "Zycie Radosne: Gawedy obozowe o prawie harcerskim" Henryk Glass
  - Harcerstwo/Boy scouts - Book, 1974 (Box-folder 83: 13)
    "O Metodzie Harcerskiej I Jej Stosowaniu" Ewa Grodecka
  - Ministerstwo Spraw Wewnetrznych - Poetry, 1985 (Box-folder 83: 14)
    Zarzad Polityczno-Wychowawczy MSW, wiersze pracownikow
  - VHS Tapes (Box-folder 84:)
  - From Archipelago Gulag to America, 1991 (Box-folder 84: 1)
    Part I and Part II, 4 tapes, Part 3, 1 tape
  - John Paul II - John Paul II and Children, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 2)
  - John Paul II - The Pope and Youth, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 3)
  - John Paul II - Pope John Paul II and the Family, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 4)
  - John Paul II - A Journalist Looks at John Paul II, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - John Paul II - The Pope and Other Faiths, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - John Paul II - A Pilgrim Pope at Marian Shrines, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 7)
  - John Paul II - The Pope and Historic Events in the East, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 8)
  - John Paul II - The Pope on Human Rights, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 9)
  - John Paul II - The Pope and the Working World, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 10)
  - John Paul II - A Day with John Paul II, 1992 (Box-folder 84: 11)
  - Dziesieciolecie Polski Niedpodleglej 1989-1999 - Book (Box-folder 85: 1)
  - Lech Kaczynski - Mug (Box-folder 85: 2)
  - Milicja Cap (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - Milicja Helmet (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - Milicja Shield (Box-folder 87: 1)
  - Milicja Baton (Box-folder 87: 2)
  - Boxes 88-91
    Boxes 88-91 are part of the Władysław Chojnacki collection and are listed at the end of the finding aid.
  - Periodicals - Dla Polski, 1915-1922 (Box-folder 92: 1)
  - Periodicals - Do Broni, 1915-1922 (Box-folder 92: 2)
  - Periodicals - Dziennik Urzedowy, 1915-1922 (Box-folder 92: 3)
  - Periodicals - Dziennik Urzedowy, 1915-1922 (Box-folder 92: 4)
  - Periodicals - Iskierka, 1915-1922 (Box-folder 92: 5)
  - Miscellaneous - Publications, 1917 (Box-folder 92: 6)
  - Peace of Riga - Treaty, 1920 (Box-folder 92: 7)
    Preliminarja Pokojowe I Ustawa o Rozejmie
  - Anti-Bolshevism - Poster, 1920 (Box-folder 92: 8)
  - Wielki Lwow - Book, 1920 (Box-folder 92: 9)
    Lwow w cyfrach
  - Identity Cards, 1938-1948 (Box-folder 92: 10)
  - Statistical Information on Poland - Publications, 1939 (Box-folder 92: 11)
  - Box 92, Folders 12-16
    Box 92, folders 12-16 are part of the Władysław Chojnacki collection and are listed at the end of the finding aid.
  - Le Service d'Information a Teheran - Publications, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 92: 17)
  - Ministerstwo Informacji I Dokumentacji - Publications, 1945 (Box-folder 92: 18)
  - Newspapers - Moscow News, 1945 (Box-folder 92: 19)
  - Periodicals - Przeglad Prasowy, 1947 (Box-folder 93: 1)
  - Periodicals - Service Civil International, 1953 (Box-folder 93: 2)
  - Newspapers - Rzeczpospolita (dodatek), 1955 (Box-folder 93: 3)
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1982 (Box-folder 93: 4)
    Jan Winiecki "Cykle inwestycyjne a inflacja popytowa w gospodarce planowej"
  - Socialist Economies - Notes, 1983 (Box-folder 93: 5)
    Jerzy Hausner "Outlines of lecture on Polish Economic Reform - Contradictions and Consequences"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1984 (Box-folder 93: 6)
    Jerzy Hausner "Socio-Political nd Economic Conditions of the Activity of the Workers Self-Management in Poland in the Period 1981-1984"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1984 (Box-folder 93: 7)
    Manuscript of "Wewnetrzne Uwarunkowania Ekonomiczne Ksztaltowania sie Sytuacji Politycznej w Polsce w 1984"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1986 (Box-folder 93: 8)
    Jan Winiecki "Why Economic Reforms Fail in the Soviet System - a Property Rights-Based Approach" manuscript
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1986 (Box-folder 93: 9)
    Jan Winiecki "Why Economic Reforms Fail in the Soviet System - a Property Rights-Based Approach"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1987 (Box-folder 93: 10)
    Jan Winiecki "Soviet-Type Economies and Reform Failures: A Touch of the Socialist Midas"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1988 (Box-folder 93: 11)
    Grzegorz W. Kolodko "Economic Reforms in Socialism"
  - Socialist Economies - Publications, 1988 (Box-folder 93: 12)
    Leszek Balcerowicz "The Soviet Type Economic System and Inovativeness"
  - Socialism - Publications, 1989 (Box-folder 93: 13--17)
    Jadwiga Staniszkis "Ontologia Socjalizmu" manuscript and final
  - Periodicals - Szczerbiec, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 94: 1)
  - Newspapers, 1995 (Box-folder 94: 2)
  - Warsaw Uprising - Questionnaires, 2001 (Box-folder 94: 3)
    Questionnaires in Bay Area
  - Art Auction - Catalogue, 2002 (Box-folder 94: 4)
  - Local Elections - General Materials (Box-folder 94: 5)
  - Local Elections - Platforma Obywatelska, 2002 (Box-folder 94: 6)
  - Local Elections - Prawo I Sprawiedliwosc (PiS), 2002 (Box-folder 94: 7)
  - Local Elections - Sojusz Lewicy Demokratycznej (SLD), 2002 (Box-folder 94: 8)
  - Local Elections - Other Parties, 2002 (Box-folder 94: 9)
  - Local Elections - Newspapers, 2002 (Box-folder 94: 10--11)
  - Box 94, folders 12-13
    Box 94, folders 12-13, are part of the Władysław Chojnacki collection and are listed at the end of the finding aid.
  - Miscellaneous - Map of Poland, circa 1920 (Box-folder 94: 14)
  - Miscellaneous - Marie Curie Museum, Undated (Box-folder 94: 15)
  - Miscellaneous - Post Cards, Undated (Box-folder 94: 16)
  - Popieluszko - Dollar Bill (Box-folder 94: 17)
  - W Marszu do Niepodleglosci - Lyrics (Box-folder 95: 1)
  - Instytut Pamieci Narodowej - Radio Free Europe, 2002 (Box-folder 95: 2)
  - EU Referendum - Newspapers (Box-folder 95: 3)
  - EU Referendum - Other Materials (Box-folder 95: 4)
  - EU Referendum - Pamphlets (Box-folder 95: 5)
  - EU Referendum - Posters (Box-folder 95: 6--7)
  - EU Referendum - Publications (Box-folder 95: 8)
  - EU Referendum - Publications (Box-folder 95: 9)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Platforma Obywatelska, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 1)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Sojusz Lewicy Demokratycznej ( SLD), 2005 (Box-folder 96: 2)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Prawo i Sprawiedliwosc (PiS), 2005 (Box-folder 96: 3)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Samoobrona RP, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 4)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Liga Polskich Rodzin (LPR), 2005 (Box-folder 96: 5)
    CD "Dokad idziesz Polsko?" - Wisniewski, Lagwa, Swiatczak
  - Presidential Elections - Kaczynski, Lech, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 6)
  - Presidential Elections - Tusk, Donald, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 7)
  - Presidential Elections - Cimoszewicz, Wlodzimierz, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 8)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Newspapers, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 9)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 10)
    Michal Kubiak "Podroz mojego zycia", book
  - Parliamentary Elections - Magazines, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 11)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2005 (Box-folder 96: 12)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2005 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - The Polish Embassy Post, 2001 (Box-folder 97: 2)
  - The Price of Freedom - Interview with Lech Walesa, 2002 (Box-folder 97: 3)
    Email with publication
  - Miscellaneous - Polska, Ukraina, Solidarnosc, 2004 (Box-folder 97: 4)
    Wybory prezydenckie na Ukrainie, 26 grudnia 2004; Vademecum obserwatora miedzynarodowego.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2007 (Box-folder 97: 5)
    "Nad Odra", Apel Antygony - List otwary w sprawie dabrowszczakow.